回家 我妻子孩子还有庄稼都在等着我
Home. My wife, my son, the harvest.
农夫马西墨斯 我还是无法想象你当农夫的样子
Maximus the farmer. I still have difficulty imagining that.
你知道的 泥垢要比血迹容易洗掉 昆塔斯
You know, dirt cleans off a lot easier than blood, Quintus.
- 他在这里 - 陛下
- Here he is. - Highness.
议员盖尔斯 议员佛克
Senator Gaius, Senator Falco.
当心盖尔斯 他会替你洗脑
Beware of Gaius. He'll pour a honeyed potion in your ear,
接着某天你醒来 就只会高喊"共和万岁 共和万岁"
and you'll wake up one day and all you'll say is, "Republic, republic, republic."
有何不可? 毕竟罗马创建时是共和制的
Well, why not? Rome was founded as a republic.
在共和制下 共和国是由元老会来执政的
Yes, and in a republic the senate has the power.
当然 议员盖尔斯绝不是因此才从政的
But Senator Gaius isn't influenced by that, of course.